你保C喜g我送的Y物
You promise you like your gift?
《我的生活》前情提要
Previously, on This Is Us...
@l毛巾  直糟透了
The towel? It's absolutely terrible.
f要纳厦姹е
He said you just go up and over
然后包起
and burrito him.
他一D眼就上大W了
They'll be in college soon.
公主陛下
Your Highness.
我斫o你找皇冠
Need to find you a crown.
我在一起相也特e愉快
We're pretty good together.
洛杉的演T淼竭@里
These L.A. actors, they come out here, right?
≡豪镫S便演小角色
They do their little stint in theater
只M足自己的s心
just to feel better about themselves.
我磉@是有正理由的
I'm here for the right reasons.
so把@ν臧  可以
Let's get this over with, shall we?
-角色o你了  -你f什么
- You got the part. - Wait, I'm sorry. What?
他X得"保姆"硌豳u
They think the nanny will sell tickets.
我一直都Σ黄鹉
I did everything wrong by you,
而你每件事都做得很
and you've done everything right.
P文砹
Look. It's Kevin.
@是我生父
This is my biological father.
@事得跟我好好聊聊啊
Wow. Well, that probably is gonna be a longer conversation,
但很高dJR你
but it's good to meet you.
幸
It's a pleasure to meet you.
一L
Long signal pass.
保迪莫破_八人防
Baltimore hopping out of an eight man front.
{R斯h投
Namath throwing deep.
接到了  _W迅速跑_接到了球
Sauer, gets wide, get it, he was there.
通^假晃\球甩_m尼・~斯...
He had an inside step on Lenny Miles...
啤酒呢
Beer.
Mommy.
卡  你e跟妹妹在@和媪
Rebecca, you and your sister need to play somewhere else.
爸爸要看球
Your father's trying to watch the game.
里克・沃克  21球T
Rick Volk, number 21,
假幼鬟\球
uh, coming with a fake
加快速度欺身而上
safety blitz and he goes up top.
@招玩得非常漂亮...
So that, um, is in pretty good...
他m然不像洛奇・比或者弗m克・哈里斯
He doesn't get all the glory of Rocky Bleier
那么功成名就  但他非常秀...
or Franco Harris, but he's been a great...
杰克
Jack.
Jack!
在
Yeah. ?
抱歉
Sorry.
我不要像我一
No. I refuse to be my mother
她盯著我爸  而我爸盯著
staring at my father as he stares at the television.
好
Okay.
辛辛那提似乎有些疲v...
I think Cincinnati's looked a little tired...
你教我吧
So teach me.
魇谙麻烨虻闹R
Teach me football.
有攻艟
We got an offensive line...
有防守  以及...
defensive line. Quart...
-蛇是得分^  -]e  有四分l
- End zone, end zone. - End zone, quarterback...
布拉德肖就在正后方
There's Bradshaw straight back...
太d了啊  布拉德肖
You suck, Bradshaw!
-什么水平  -
- Come on, man. ?- Babe...
他拿^三次超碗冠
The man has three Super Bowl rings.
-e太著急  -可他居然
- Give him a break. - Yeah, he also
弗m科如入o人之地
had Franco wide open in the flat.
你不防守  布拉德肖
You're a freakin' bum, Bradshaw.
不防守
You're a freakin' bum.
他@
Typical Bradshaw.
超碗
Super Bowl!
-上路啦  -@么快
- Time to tailgate! ?- Oh, already?
]e  我得走了  青蛙酒吧要_前派
Yeah, babe. I got to move. Froggy's wants me to sing
我^去唱歌
at their pre-game party.
-周日的超碗比  -
- Super Bowl Sunday? ?- Yeah.
一年中就今天人最多
Biggest crowd of the whole year.
-而且我可以免M喝  -太好了
- And we get to drink for free. - Oh, yeah.
你得早c去
So be there early, okay?
布拉德肖那老家伙]_始嵘
I'll be there before Bradshaw even begins
我就已到隽
warming up his old noodle arm.
e@么f他
Easy on Bradshaw, babe.
在我家不S@
Not in this house.
真是我家
That's my girl. ?
米格和雪莉能去
Are Miguel and Shelly gonna make it?
能  他f到r候
Yeah. They're gonna meet us there, you know,
不^要看他能不能找到保姆
depending on if they can get a babysitter,
而且不能跟上次一
and one that doesn't show up completely
找嗑得神志不清的a君子
stoned out of her gourd this time.
到底槭裁匆生孩子
Why do people have kids?
不是很懂
No idea.
好吧
All right.
你好
You okay?
住手
Stop.
m德  醒醒
Randall, wake the hell up.
你都把化放M你的奶昔里了
You almost put a chemo pill in your shake.
P文大伯
Uncle Kevin,
你槭裁丛上yy
why are you writing in your book?
小  @是”
Play, sweetheart. It's a play,
а菹Ｍ我能做c鼍氨硌
and the director wants me doing scene work.
可你似乎一直在
You seem to be doing a lot of writing.
因樘多人告V我怎么做了  威廉
Well, I seem to be getting a lot of direction, William.
其  你的音很不e
Tell you what. You got a great voice.
有]有^配音
You ever do any voice-over work?
Well, you should.
真的  你可以去演...
Really. I mean, you could be a...
比如赢影片里的^
like a... like a... like an owl in a Pixar movie,
-Π  -_玩笑
- right? ?- Yeah.
-o意冒犯  -@有什么冒犯的
- No offense. - Not sure why I would take offense to that.
我不吃{莓
Oh, I don't do blueberries.
-我也不吃  -你啥r候_始不吃了
- Me neither. - Since when?
-今天_始  -是吧
- Since now. - Yeah.
都不f味道如何
It's not the taste, right?
{莓皮那口感  太盒牧
It's the texture of the skin, it's gross.
我也不想吃{莓了
Yeah. I don't want blueberries either.
好的]}  有]有其他忌口
Yeah. Understood. Uh, any other dietary restrictions
我跟N房的人f一下
I should let the staff know about?
算了  你那么忙
No, man. You're busy. I'll just, you know,
回^我有空o你列巫影
I'll make a list for you later when I get some time.
x了
Thanks, buddy.
你得先吃c|西||胃  威廉
You need to put something in your stomach, William.
吐司  片和果汁  按@序  好
Toast, pills, juice. That's the order. Okay?
你是在吃
Is that medicine?
你是不是感冒了
Do you have a cold, Grandpa?
-]事  -只是S生素
- Grandpa's fine. - No. They're just vitamins.
@么f
So.
她z知道他是
You, uh, told the girls that he's Grandpa,
但不知道他病了
but not that he's sick. Right?
@雍苊半U
That's ballsy.
P文
Hey, so, Kevin, uh,
自哪翘炷氵^
it's been a few days now, you know,
-就一直住在@里  -也]提前打
- since you showed up. - Without calling.
-  -到你我很_心
- Right. - And... and it's great to see you.
就是想下...
I was just sort of wondering...
怎么比^Y貌呢
How do I say this politely?
你什么r候走
When are you leaving?
就@意思
Yeah. Yeah.
@啊
Yeah.
我  我  @ 我Sr...
No, I mean, come on. I can, I... I can, um...
我Sr可以走  就是...
I can get out of here whenever. I just... I...
我想著便可以砼闩隳
I saw this as an opportunity to hang with you two,
有z小  不^...
you know, and the girls, but, uh...
其f  @”
Plus I... honestly, this play, guys,
我有c^疼
it's kicking my ass a little, You know? ?
而且一人住酒店太孤了
And it's so lonely at that hotel.
我一人住大套g
I mean, I got this big suite all to myself,
但是房g越大  就越寂寞
but I guess the bigger the hotel room, the emptier it can feel.
我就坐在那
You know? I'm sitting there.
m然那里有八百的高|量床
I got that 800 thread count sheets.
迷你冰箱里也有吃不完的小吃
I got the endless minibar snacks.
有高的燕香皂和L毛q睡袍
You got the fancy oatmeal soaps, plush robes
而我就只坐在那
and all I can do is sit there
默默地想著
and think about how...
太安o了
quiet it is.
-我要了  -什么
- We'll take it. - What's that?
酒店  我和z  我今晚就去住
The hotel. Beth and I, we'll take it, tonight.
不  m德  我Rr去哪找保姆呢
No, Randall. Where are we gonna get a sitter?
不  我有晌患胰
No, We got two family members
-不不不  -免M住在咱家
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no. - living in our house for free.
有一在上演^保姆
One of them played a nanny on TV.
不不  H上是Q工住宿生
No. ?No, actually, an au pair.
蚀_的f  我在上演的是Q工住宿生
Technically, I played an au pair on TV.
@烧呤怯^e的  很多人都不知道
There's a difference. A lot of people don't know that.
我演的是一Q工住宿生
I was... an au pair.
他本想管@〗惺裁础Q工住宿生》  但...
They were gonna call the show what Au Pair, but the...
叫"保姆"效果更好  我可以照孩子
Manny tested better. I-I can watch the girls.
-我去收拾行李  -好
- I'm-a go pack. ?- Okay.
我F在去收拾行李
I'm-a go pack right now.
早安
Good morning.
在床上吃早餐
Breakfast in bed?
是的
Yeah.
我做了什么能享受@N待遇呢
What did I do to deserve this?
f不好啊
I don't know.
你槲易隽颂多N心的事
You've done a lot of really nice things for me,
所以我想回竽
so I wanted to return the favor.
把"硬板"切成方K  放到碗里
Oh. By cutting up cardboard into little squares
砘笪
and putting it in a bowl?
@些是奶酪K
Those are cheese squares.
"美味啊"
Oh, yum.
上面是什么
Yeah. What's on top?
大麻籽
Oh, hemp seed.
大麻籽⒃谏厦
Hemp seeds on top?
你可真避重就p
Boy, you really buried the lede.
我要吃啦
?Now I'm in.
怎么了  你不要吃c什么黑暗料理
?What? You're not gonna have any nonsense made-up food?
不  下午我的互助上要Q重的
No. Getting weighed at our meeting this afternoon.
你知道
You know what?
我也是
So am I.
我或S也不吃了  死的
I probably shouldn't eat, either. Damn.
互助Y束后  你想做什么
?Hey, what do you want to do after the meeting?
我想去打迷你高夫
I was thinking miniature golf.
上一次  我不到20U就打M了18洞
Last time I was like, 20 under going into the 18th,
但那迷你Lv了y
but that little windmill owns my ass.
去不了  要看人比
I can't. Steelers.
周日橄烨蛑夜
Sunday Night Football. ?
Sunday Night Football.
和l一起
With who?
]e人  就我一
Oh, no one. Just me.
好吧  我陪你一起看
All right. I'll watch with you.
不用了  xx  我自己看就行了
Oh, no. Thanks, but I'm good.
真的
Seriously?
你愿一人看也不愿和我一起看
You'd rather watch by yourself than watch with me?
是的  那是我的人酆
Yeah. It's my thing.
我有@T  你懂吧  人酆
I have a little ritual. You know? It's my thing.
好吧  你的人酆...
Well, your thing...
很悲哀啊
is sad.
我不X得
Not to me.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  不如@影
Okay. How about this?
你可以看橄烨
You can watch football...
你一人看
all by yourself,
@很正常  但是要和我一起
which is totally normal, but with me.
托比
Toby. ?
我就垡人看球
This is something that I do alone. Okay?
好吧
Sure.
太好了  xx你@么wN
Great. Thank you for being so sweet.
你能臀医o@加一碗糖
Can you bring, like, a bowl of sugar for this?
*如果你愿意o我*
*And if you give me*
*大麻*
*Weed*
*白葡萄酒*
*Whites*
*和t葡萄酒*
*And wine*
*o我一c暗示*
*And you show me a sign*
*那么我就*
*I'll be*
*我就愿意*
*Willin' to be*
*前行*
*Movin'.*
xx大家  人加油
Thank you. Go, Steelers!
x天x地K于完了  能看比了
Thank God. Can we please watch the game now?
g迎^m收看玫瑰碗
The Rose Bowl is back.
第十四贸碗
@里座o席
Not an empty seat anywhere.
-借^一下  -唱得太棒了
- Excuse me. - That was amazing.
-真的  -真的
- Ah, yeah? Really? - ?Yeah.
雪莉  米格
Oh! Shelly, Miguel.
他到了
There they are.
-真抱歉我t到了  -]事的
- So sorry we're late. - It's okay.
-真是Σ黄  -都是因楹⒆
- Oh, I'm so sorry. - Damn, kids, man.
我正涑鲩T
We were just about to head out the door,
小就_始I吐
and the baby decides to projective vomit
吐得小安迪M身都是
all over little Andy.
-也差c吐到我身上  -你猜安迪做了什么
- Almost got me, too. - So, what does Andy do?
你知道的  才四q  w型像坦克一
You know, four years old, built like a tank.
他扇了小一耳光
He slaps the baby.
就扇在上  啪的一
Right across the face. Pow!
-不是吧  她好  -她]事
- No! Is she okay? - Oh, she's fine. Yeah.
然后小就_始拼命尖叫
But then the baby's screaming bloody murder,
我也朝安迪喊
I'm screaming at Andy,
我就站在那  身上都是I吐物  我就f
and me, standing there, covered in vomit, and I'm like,
安迪  她是
Andy, she is a baby.
你竟然扇了一阂话驼
Like, you literally slapped a baby.
@真是土倒忙  可想而知
Which really helped, as you can imagine.
]e  安迪也_始哭
Of course, then Andy starts crying,
-小哭  保姆也哭  -去喝c|西吧
- baby's crying, babysitter's crying. - We need drinks!
我去喝c|西吧  一就回
We need drinks. We'll be right back.
好的
Okay.
跟我保C我永h不要孩子
Promise me we are never having kids.
喝c炮酒了
I think it's time for shots.
有人被涞搅
Somebody's down.
26球T今天\獠缓冒
26 is having a tough day.
我的生活
第一季  第五集
公羊上半鼍挂13比10的比分
The first half, the Rams, surprisingly,
-I先匹堡人  -真d啊
- lead Pittsburgh 13 to 10. - Pathetic.
]有k法阻踹M攻
Can't stop the run.
布拉德肖真
Oh, and Bradshaw sucks!
不  布拉德肖在下半霰l的
Oh, no, Bradshaw's gonna have a huge second half, though.
H鄣
Right, babe?
是的  下半龃蟊l
Yeah. Big... big second half.
你好
Are you okay?
很好
Mm. Fine.
好吧
Okay.
其不好
Actually, no.
你之前那是什么意思...
What did you mean before when, uh...
就是你f...
when you said...
"跟我保C我永h不要孩子"
"Promise me we'll never have kids"?
我不那诱f的
Oh. I shouldn't have said that.
]e  但是你f了
Yeah, but... you did.
今天好像f了纱
Kind of said it twice today.
我不f的
And I shouldn't have.
好
Okay?
Σ黄
Sorry.
你知道我怎么做
You know what we need to be doing?
我多o弗m科髑  Π
We need to be feeding the ball to Franco more, right?
-@才...  -我矶疾徽@事
-That's... -?'Cause we-we never really talk about it.
我F在也不想@事
And I don't want to talk about it now, either.
我是f以后再f
We always say we're gonna talk about it in the future,
但F在就是的r候了  小
but it's the future now, Bec,
我想要孩子
and I want kids.
我再去吧_拿妆酒^
You know what, we're gonna go grab another drink at the bar.
看看粉z的情r
and see how the fans--
F在我碚姜人和保_・宏{
Let's go to the Ginger Man and Paul Hornung. ?
洛杉粉z肯定高d牧  保_
L.A. Fans have to be happy, Paul.
睡Xrg是八c和九c
Bedtimes are at 8:00 and 9:00,
八c刷完牙  九c要上床
that's teeth brushed, in the bed. 8:00 and 9:00.
就是茴香酒就著安眠喝下去
So one Sambuca to chase down the Ambien,
然后就熄  Π
and then lights out, right?
玩笑_^^了
That's too far.
著  放心吧
Okay, listen, relax.
我今晚乖乖待在家的
We're gonna have a nice, quiet evening at home. Okay?
孩子玩自己的
The girls are gonna play.
我要熟_~  背下
I'm gonna memorize my lines and get off book.
明一下  一般情r下
Look, we want to make it clear that we're not normally
我是不晚上为留她在家的
in the habit of leaving the girls overnight.
更ef交oz]怎么和孩子打^交道的人了
Let alone with two men who probably haven't been around kids that much.
其中一把自己的孩子z在了消防局
One of them's best known for leaving a kid at a fire station.
天  千f要照好我的孩子
Oh, my God, please, take care of my babies.
有  eo我打
And, please, don't call us.
不不  如果需要我就打
No, no, call us if you need us.
最好e需要我
But don't need us.
在你走之前  有一件事
Oh, one more thing, though, before you go.
苔z就是
So, Tess was the, uh,
喜g喝白葡萄酒  是吧
the white wine drinker, right?
然后安妮喜g喝t酒  我可不想搞混了
Annie likes the red 'cause I don't get that wrong.
惹得她不高d
Piss them off.
是有c^^了  我哪的表情看出砹
It's still too far. I can tell by the way you...
玩笑是有c^^了
Yes. ?It's a little too far.
-他太不正了  -]P系的
- He plays too much. ?- It's okay.
-]P系的  -太不正了
- It's okay. - He plays too much.
如果有需要就o我打
Hey, call us if you need anything.
e打
Don't call us.
我在控制干食用量方面有}
So, I have, you know, this-this issue with-with cracker control,
我lF很有椭的方法
so what I've been finding to be really helpful ?
就是...
is if I...
把干暮凶永锬贸
take the portion out of the box
然后把干放在P子上
and then I put the portion onto the plate
-把盒子  -f^去就行了
- and then I put the box - Just pass it.
放得hh的  然后我就知道我只能吃
away, and then I know how-how many crackers
多少K干了
I'm allowed to-to have.
f^去就行了
Just pass it.
多少K干
To h -- to have.
我知道了如果我只能吃十K干
So then I know that if-if I'm only allowed to have ten crackers,
我就只放十K干在P子里
then I have the ten crackers on my plate,
@挺好的  但是同r
which is fine, but at the same time,
τ谝恍╋干碚f
there are other crackers that I like than-than
我更喜g吃另外的追N干
other crackers. So, I might not like
比如我更喜g吃芝士干
saltine crackers as much as I like
而不是很喜gK打干
a Cheez-It type cracker,
你被邀⒓油斜鹊"人"派
那么我τ谥ナ匡干
but so, what I'll do with the Cheez-It type cracker
|地得分  加油人
我也S多放K在P子里
is maybe put a little bit more on the plate,
但我是栏窨刂盗
but I'm still rationing,
所以如果是K打干  我放十K在P子里
so if I have a saltine, then I might put ten on the plate,
如果是芝士干  就放二十K
but there might be 20 if it's a Cheez-It. ?
但我是把盒子拿_  所以
But I still put the box away. So, I-I mean
我X得@也算是一N倮吧
I-I think that's -- that's a win.
她是出差
She was always away on business.
我已T孤了  但是@...
So, I was used to being alone but this, you know, this...
@是另外一N孤
but this was a different kind of alone.
她是出差  我已T了...
She was always away on business, so I was used to being...
但是  我...
but... so, I was...
她是出差  我已T孤了
She was always away on business, so I was used to being alone,
但是@是另外一N孤
but this was a different kind of alone.
@是另外一N孤
You know? This-this is a different kind of...
你不是在看影
I thought you two were watching a movie.
我想ek一霭疟韧尥rb秀
We want to have a Barbie fashion show.
不e呀  上去很好玩
Oh, cool. That sounds fun.
去玩芭比娃娃rb秀吧
So, go play Barbie fashion show.
我想你明星u委
We need you to be the celebrity judge.
@
Right.
但是我不行
Uh, the thing is I can't,
因槊魈煲排了
because I got this rehearsal tomorrow
而且我很想稿  所以...
and I really want to be off book, so...
"稿"是什么意思
What does "Off book" mean?
稿  稿的意思就是
Off book. Off book means, uh,
意思就是我背下了_~
means that I know my lines.
u委好了
Have Grandpa be the judge.
不是明星呀
Grandpa's not a celebrity.
是呀
Yeah.
她的挺合理的
Their logic seems sound.
xx你了
Thank you.
@影  你想不想
Okay. Um... tell you what? You want to,
你想臀  想不想
you want to help me? You want to,
想不想和我一起念_~
you want to read the play with me?
-好呀  -戆戆
- Okay. - ?Yeah. Oh, come on.
-可以  -戆戆
- Okay. ?- Yeah, let's do that.
戆  磉@  威廉
Come on, over here. William,
-快戆  -我可不是什么演T
- let's do it. - I'm not much of an actor.
@]P系
Oh, doesn't matter.
我只需要有人砟钜幌屡_~
I just need to get the lines down, so...
苔z  哪汩_始
All right, Tess, we'll start with you.
你演杰西卡  大l的妻子
Uh, you're gonna be Jessica, David's wife.
{什么她可以演杰西卡
Why does she get to be Jessica?
因槟阊莞窭孜
Oh, because you're Gracie, okay?
格雷西是杰西卡的  很酷
Gracie's Jessica's mom, which is kind of cool.
你可以δ憬憬泐U指馐沽
It means you get to boss your sister around.
怎么  不e吧
How's that sound?
威廉  有很多}
So. William, multiple questions.
第一}  老f
First one, I'm not gonna lie to you,
-@}有c微妙  -吧
- it's a little delicate. - ?Go ahead.
你R字
Do you know how to read?
我R字
Yes, I can read.
我知道  我是跟你_玩笑呢
I knew it. I was joking.
你然R字了
Of course you know how to read.
和你_玩笑呢
Trying to be funny. Okay.
你能不能念一下布拉德的_~
So if you could please read the role of Brad.
好O了  你去哪
Terrific, okay. Whoa, where we going?
我要尿尿
I have to pee.
我也要去尿尿
Oh, I kind of do, too.
你怎么...我的天
What are you... Oh, good God.
@才像勇
Now, this is what I'm talking about.
@影才
Okay, babe, here's the plan.
先做
Sex first.
R上就做
Right away.
震耳欲@  翻云覆雨
Loud, adult,
不用忌隔壁有小孩的那N
no kids in the next room sex.
而且不用硎裁葱垴R拉松
And it doesn't have to be marathon sex.
我只要搞定@活
We just need to get the job done.
有在看完《房人》之前
And under no circumstances are we allowed
l都不氏人著
to fall asleep afterwards watching House Hunters.
不能整晚都浪M在睡X上  Π
Don't want to miss the whole night sleeping. Right?
我要淋浴做
We'll do it in the shower.
超爽
That's good.
可e在豪A淋浴g睡著了
Won't fall asleep in the big fancy shower.
在此之前我得先叫客房服
And we'll order room service before.
@右  在Y束成人式淋浴放性酆
That way we will finish our loud adult shower sex
正好砜头糠  我就可以穿著浴袍
just as room service arrives and we will slip on robes
啃h堡  不  慢著  意大利面
and eat burgers... No, wait-- spaghetti.
不  我是喜gh堡
No, I like burgers better.
我要躺在床上啃h堡
We will eat burgers in bed.
F在PI的}是
Oh. Now, the big question is...
看什么付M目好呢
what to order on pay-per-view.
我真希望他@有
Oh, I already hope they, uh,
休・格m特和梅・斯特里普的影
I hope they have that Huge Grant-Meryl Streep movie that
@名字著像女黑人  瞧瞧
sounds like a black lady. Come on.
《跑{天后》
Florence Foster Jenkins.
他@有《跑{天后》
Baby, they already got Florence Foster Jenkins.
我月t了
I'm late.
t了一周半  m德
I'm a week and a half late, Randall,
我感X糟透了
and I feel like crap.
昨天一整天我都在嚼冰
And I was chewing on ice all day yesterday
看到披_的r候我差c吐了
and I almost threw up when I looked at pizza
而且我k不到自己一人去店
and I cannot bring myself to go to the drugstore
I孕棒
and get a pregnancy test.
我氐谆帕
I'm bugging out, baby.
你得我冷o下
I need you to talk me down.
-你好  -很好
- Hey, how are you? ?- Hey, good.
M戆  我有胡}卜  芹菜
Come on in. We got carrots, celery,
西m花  o蘸u  不用客
broccoli, no dip. You're welcome.
xx  真不e
Thank you, that's so nice.
P特  @是我好朋友  舒特
Oh, and, uh, Kate, this is my good friend, Shooter.
舒特  @是P特
Shooter, Kate.
很高dJR你  P特
Nice to finally meet you, Kate.
我也是
Hi. Nice to meet you, too.
好消息  你都喜gw育  所以...
Great news. You both love sports, so...
w育派
sports party.
你怎么看  杰克
So, what do you think, Jack?
比R上就要M入第四了
Looking like it's gonna come down to the fourth quarter.
你想F在  好吧  我碚
You want to do this now? Okay. Let's do it.
那么
So...
我δ碚f不
I am not enough for you.
你有我不  杰克
Am I not enough for you, Jack?
-撤回吧_  -好的
- Okay, back to the bar? - Yep.
我]@么f  我是f
I never said that. I just meant
@}我w是要的
we need to have this conversation at some point.
可你非要F在  在@青蛙酒吧
Okay. And you want to do that right now, at Froggy's
-超碗直播的r候  -是啊
- during the Super Bowl? - Yes,
麻┰俅舐c  e我e^你的好
please don't make us miss a second of your drama.
你能e管e事
Could you butt out?
我一直拿@事_玩笑
Babe, we joke about it.
我看e人е孩子  就f
We see people with kids and go,
"x天x地  幸不是咱z"
"Oh, thank God that's not us."
我拿它_玩笑  不是
We joke about it. Right?
y道我理解e了
Did I not get the joke?
我不是...
I'm not...
你是Φ
Babe, you're right.
You are right.
就我成L的家庭而言
And coming from the family that-that I did,
我]想^要自己的孩子
I definitely never saw myself having kids.
-好的  -但后砦矣鲆了你
- Okay. ?- But then I met you.
而且  我在一起很快
And, you know, we're j... we're great together
我喜g我的生活
and I love our life.
但S著年g增L  我越lX得...
But the older we get, the more I think that...
我越lX得有超越你我扇
the more I think there's got to be something bigger
更有意x的事
than just me and you.
真是xx你把我加入
Well, thank you very much for involving me
你o形的巨大化中  超巨大
in this huge invisible change of yours. Huge.
因樵谀阌鲆我  直到娶了我
Because you knew when you met me and married me
就知道我不是那N
that I did not want to be one of those women
把成槟赣H作槿松唯一目说呐人
whose sole purpose in life was to be a mother.
如果那是你想要的  你初就娶我
If that's what you wanted, you should have married my mom.
我更希望是你妹妹
I was thinking more your sister.
我估也是
Oh. You probably were.
我只是...@玩笑不好笑
I'm... it's a bad joke.
我]浜  杰克
I'm not there yet, Jack.
我]浜
I'm not there yet.
-我才29  -快30了
- I am only 29. - ?Almost 30.
我知道自己q
I know how old I am!
席德和南茜  你z能出去吵
Hey, Sid and Nancy, will you two take it outside?
《席德c南茜》1986年影
髌uL逢吉他手席德c其女友南茜相巯
-你能]嘴不  -管好你自己的事
- Could you just shut up for a second? - Mind your business.
大伙都被你吵得不球了
None of us can hear the game over your mouth.
你得WWY貌了  老兄
You got to learn some manners, pal.
你得管好你的女人
You need to control your woman.
你f小心c
You need to watch your mouth.
杰克  坐下
Jack, sit down.
回  ]必要吵
Come here. It's not worth it.
杰克  坐下  求你了
Jack, sit down, please.
杰克
Jack.
-天啊  杰克  -杰克  杰克
- God, Jack. - ?Jack! Jack.
不  不  不  不
No! No, no, no, no.
是啊
Yeah,
我真要孩子
we should really be having kids.
店
你不想fc什么
Aren't you gonna say anything?
好吧  @怎么可能
Uh, yeah. Like, how?
-你每天都有按r吃吧  -]e
- You take the pill every day like clockwork, right? - Yeah.
是我又不小心把哪粒GM我奶昔里了
What, did I accidentally drop one in my shake or something?
不  我...
No. I...
我上月Q了
I mean, I changed medications last month
可能出F了短旱呐怕哑
and there might have been, like, a brief window.
短旱呐怕哑
A brief window?
抱歉
Sorry.
短旱呐怕哑  z
A brief window, Beth?
y道你]想^跟你的丈夫
Did it not occur to you that that might be something
提@件事
you want to run by your husband?
我又不知道出}
Well, I didn't know it was gonna be a problem.
查斯D泡了
Well, there goes Charleston.
抱歉  你f什么
Okay, I'm sorry, what?
十年之后  等女都去上大W了
Ten years from now, when the girls are both off at college,
我想我可以早些退休移居查斯D
I thought that we would take an early retirement in Charleston.
不好意思  m德
Oh, forgive me, Randall,
可你到底在f什么鬼
but what in the holy hell are you talking about?
你什么r候_始想搬去查斯D了
Since when do you want to move to Charleston?
我看到上的介B
I saw something about it on CNN.
在那可以享受高|量生活  高n餐d
Like, they got a great quality of life, good restaurants.
工作e暇r  我也上W搜搜
Sometimes at work, I look up places on Zillow.
好吧  我真的非常抱歉
Oh, okay. Well, I'm so sorry that
你最高C密的查斯D之羝扑榱
I'm screwing with your super top secret Charleston dream, honey.
我的}和你的相比不值一提
No, my issues are nothing compared to yours.
-]人@么f  -等等  等等
- Nobody's saying that. - Wait,wait, wait, wait, wait,
聿iZ
here's a riddle--
是l做好一切渲胤倒ぷ位
who has two hands and was about to go back to work full-time
@或S...或S能她找回那暗淖约
and maybe, maybe... start to remember who she was?
好
Yeah?
可F在她只能把rg花在
But now will have to split her time between
Q尿布_和家庭k公室了
a diaper station and a home office?
@女人  就在此
This girl, right here.
-是筛拇指  -什么
- It's two thumbs. - ?What?
你姿莶
You're doing it wrong.
你f"l用筛拇指
You're supposed to say what has two thumbs and is
-把rg花在..."  -]嘴
- gonna be splitting time betw..." - ?Shut up.
好的  都你的  z
Okay, that's real nice, Beth.
-一l口香糖  -麻┝
- Also, some Altoids. - ?Please.
瞧瞧@面
Look at that picture.
太清晰了
That is a vivid picture.
就像在F隹匆
I feel like I'm at the game.
跑^了
Over across the field, here.
@是挺不e
Yeah. It's a really nice TV...
@是什么屏
What is this?
等x子
Plasma?
LED
LED?
我不太清楚  但...
You know, I'm really not sure, but...
托比
Hey, Toby!
什么事
Yeah?
-你鄢鍪  -等x子是LED
- Uh, do you guys like jicama? - ?Plasma or LED?
我...
I...
不知道
have no idea.
-P特  鍪  -什么
- Kate? Jicama? ?- What?
@是蔬菜是水果
Is that a vegetable or a fruit?
能挪地  小托
Can... can you actually just move, Tob?
好好好
Oh! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yep.
外接手到位了
The receiver's all set.
往右  本看著中g
To the right, Ben looks straight over the middle,
跑向_^
and going for the end zone!
舒特  跟P特ff
Shooter, uh, tell Kate
那次我`打`撞
about that time we accidentally
去了艾希莉・辛普森演唱的事
went to an Ashlee Simpson concert.
真得跟你ff
Uh, you got to hear this.
-我r是想...  -不好意思
- So, we were trying to... - I'm sorry.
托比  你按了和
Toby, you paused the TV.
就@和Ａ
It's like, paused.
是啊  就一  你他f
Yeah, just for a second. Listen to this.
真的值得一
No, this is a great story.
不  好吧
No. O-Okay,
其]什么
I know it's not a big deal, really,
只不^我比^喜g
but I kind of like to watch sports
看球直播
as they happen live.
可能只有我@影
Probably just me, right?
-我不知道  -好  好  我^m
- I don't know. - Okay. Okay. Here we go.
-像是在等...  -我延r了
- ...tends to wait... - Now we're behind the game!
快M
Fast forward it!
|地得分
Touch down!
海沃德全程自己一人淖韧...
And Heyward made it all alone down the left side...
害  你喜g的球是吧
That's great. That's your team, right?
我心中的糁
That's my fantasy team.
-那是什么  -跟你f
- What's that? - ?You know what,
抱歉打嘁幌
I'm so sorry to interrupt,
我不太舒服
I'm actually not feeling good.
我得先走了
I'm gonna go ahead and go.
不吧
Oh, no!
真的要走了
Are you sure?
P特  留下吧
No, Kate, stay.
舒特
Shooter...
-很高d到你  -很高d到你
- It was really nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
-什么  等等  -J真的
- What... wait, wait, wait. - Seriously,
-xx你做了鍪  -什么
- thank you for the jicama. - ?What...
晚c再聊
I'll talk to you later.
怎么了
What is happening?
你得放下她  大l
You have to let her go, David.
@犹不理智了
This is crazy, man.
她走了  不再回砹
She's gone and she's never coming back.
你之前真的]演^
You really never acted before?
]
Nope.
zI一般的嗓音
Voice like silk.
我怎么放得下  大l
How am I supposed to move on, David?
不  我是大l
No. I'm David.
我怎么放得下  布拉德
How am I supposed to move on, Brad?
你{什么裎曳畔
And who made you the expert of moving on?
你{什么f我
Or the expert of anything for that matter?
你打算就@么演
Is that how you're gonna do it?
不是
No.
那就好
Good.
到你了
It's your line.
苔z  H鄣  下一句是你了
Tess, honey, you have the next line.
集中注意力
Pay attention.
我...我不希望你放下
?I-I'd rather you not move on. I'm--
我...我@然]@打算
I'm obv-- I'm obviously not planning to.
不好
It's not good.
]你想的那么容易是吧
Not as easy as it looks, is it?
-是的  -是吧  好
- No. - ?No. Okay.
她在那  你看她了
There she is! Do you see her?
l  大l  我看到l了
Who, David? Did I see who?
她啊  她就在那
Her! She's right there.
在她死后
And ever since she died,
她的鬼魂就一直跟著我
her ghost has been haunting me.
等等
Hold up.
怎么了  H鄣
What's the matter, sweetheart?
@是什么故事
What's happening in this story?
你]懂@故事
You're not following the story?
你懂了
Do you follow it?
然  我然懂
Of course. Yes, of course I follow it.
她死了是吧
She died, right?
她死了
She's dead.
但她的鬼魂一直魂不散
But she keeps coming back as a ghost.
所以你死后就成鬼
So when you die you become a ghost?
不
No.
不不不  H鄣  鬼都是假的
No, no, no, no, no. No. Sweetheart, ghosts aren't real.
那你死了之后l生什么
So what happens when you die?
你死了之后l生什么
What happens when you die?
你就死了
Uh, is... you die.
永h
Forever?
是的  也可能不是
Sure... or not.
我不知道  H鄣  是@拥
I don't know. Honey, here's the thing, you know,
你想不想要鬼  我可以...
do we want ghosts or do we not want ghosts? Because I can...
因樯病了吃
Grandpa takes pills because he's sick,
死
is Grandpa gonna die?
槭裁匆我
Why are you asking me this?
吧
Yes? Yes.
快了
Soon?
跟你f
Well, you know, I mean,
我是你的就不投入太多感情...
I wouldn't get too attached if I were you, so...
不  不不不
No! No, no, no.
我不是@意思  我是@么f
That's not what I meant. Look, I-I mean, I meant it,
但我只是想活S夥  是笑  好
but I was trying to be fun... It was a joke, okay?
死亡是一件很自然的事
Here's the thing about death, is that it's natural.
是自然律  我也死  明白
It's just natural. I'm gonna die, okay?
你z  你也死
You two? You're gonna die.
爸爸也死
Mommy and Daddy are gonna die.
-爸爸死  -不是...
- Mommy and Daddy are gonna die? - No. Uh...
著...我的天  rg不早了
Look, uh, oh, my gosh, Wil... it is getting late.
要睡X了  孩子
It's bedtime, girls.
-戆  孩子  -Φ
- Come on, girls. - Yep.
睡X了  睡好X
Time to go to bed. Uh, sleep tight.
xx你臀
Thanks for all the help.
e忘了刷牙
Don't forget to brush your teeth.
你什么r候Q定要小孩的
Wh-when did you guys know you wanted kids?
大概是在她第一次言械乃月后
Uh, about, uh, four months into her first pregnancy.
卡X得如果我有了小孩
Rebecca thinks that if we have kids,
我的生活就完了
our lives are gonna be over.
她f得  哥
She's right, pal. Yeah.
她f得
She's totally right.
那r你可以跟生活f再了
You can kiss this life good-bye.
如果她不想要小孩呢
What if she doesn't want kids?
@真的有那么重要  不惜[僵
Is that really like a, like a deal-breaker?
我去找雪莉
I got to go find Shelly.
被人o截球了
That over the wrong shoulder.
@是有史以碜罹彩的一次接球
That's one of the great catches you'll ever see.
近67米
73 yards.
玫瑰碗最害的球
And the terrible towels will come out
就要Q生了
throughout the Rose Bowl.
l是最佳球已毋庸置疑
Not much doubt about the best team.
@悉  由w育s志及其投票F
Just been informed that the MVP for this contest
青蛙酒吧
xe的本次比
as picked by Sport Magazine
出口
最佳球T是特里・布拉德肖
and their panel of voters is Terry Bradshaw.
@可不是我今晚的
This isn't the night I had planned.
我知道
I know.
要看
Shall we look?
等等  我...
Wait. Just, um, let's... let's...
我再等三十秒吧
let's give it like, 30 more seconds.
好
Okay.
你仍然可以接更多工作
You'll still be able to work more.
我可以p少工作量
I can work less.
我可以找保姆
We'll get a nanny.
或者"n男保姆"
Or a manny.
天啊  不要
God, no.
如果你想去
You know, if you still want
-什么度假屋  你可以...  -不要了
- that vacation house, you can... - ?I don't.
太麻┝
It's too much trouble.
要心ZL
Worrying about hurricanes
要心不有小孩JM
and whether or not it gets broken into by some kids
用...  l知道干嘛呢
using it for their who knows what?
南卡_R{州的小混混
Damn South Carolina punk-ass kids.
有鹤不太糟
You know, a son wouldn't totally suck.
我生的孩子都很棒
We do make good kids.
是啊  都很棒
That we do, that we do.
姑娘喜g的
The girls will love it.
她矾的
Oh, they'll go nuts.
是l有筛拇指
What has two thumbs
如此地深壑自己的妻子
and loves his wife so much it hurts?
f"筛拇指"_好一些
Oh, it does work better with two thumbs.
不  我是喜g你的方式
Nah. I like the way you do it.
@影...  那我喜g你的表情
Mm. Well... I like your face.
要看看
Shall we do this?
才的交流x控制了  Π
Well, that conversation went sideways, didn't it?
m德知道了一定揍我的
Randall's gonna punch me for that conversation.
我得去和孩子
I got to go talk to the girls.
和孩子...  我f什么呢
Go talk to the girls-- what am I gonna say?
我@然不是那
You know, I am clearly not the man
能蚝退
that needs to be talking to them
@些生死之的碗s}的人
about the intricacies of life and death.
@在...
It's...
你是@
You do that a lot.
我是怎么
I do what a lot?
岩勺约
Doubt yourself.
你演得很好  P文
You were very good, Kevin.
在那±
On that show.
你看了《n男保姆》
You watched The Manny?
磉@里之前  有_fC
Before I came here, I had one old television,
只有三_能看
got three channels.
我非常喜g那目
I really liked that program.
我r想  @人真有才啊
And I remember thinking, he's very talented.
我喜g你失去的那集
I liked the one where you lose the baby.
天啊
Oh, geez.
《男保姆l火》
"Manny on Fire."
是啊  那集...
Yeah, you know. That was a...
那集非常精彩
That was a strong episode.
-]e  -是啊
- Yeah. ?- Yeah, yeah.
我真不退出那部
I never should have left that show.
我...
I've...
我不磉@里的  毫o疑
I never should have come here, that's for sure.
^碚疹侄女  演什么...
Being an uncle, right, doing theater...
我...
I... I...
我根本不是演〉牧
I'm not cut out for theater.
你又_始了
And there you go again.
好吧  你f起砣菀装  Π
Well, yeah, I mean, that's easy for you to say, right?
你就是皮克斯赢片里那只明的^
You're the wise owl in a Pixar film.
而我是那只愚蠢的拉布拉多犬
I'm the dopey Labrador.
我是x死不h的戒了毒的a君子
I'm a dying recovering addict.
-S你f了  -明的^f了
- Yeah, whatever. - ?Yeah, well, people love Labradors.
人都喜g拉布拉多
Said the wise owl.
你知道是怎么回事
You want to know what it is?
在@部蚶
It's this play, right?
和我一起工作的那些人
I mean, these people that I'm working with,
他直比我明一e
wow, they're like next level smart.
我是f  他太秀了
I mean, uh, they're brilliant.
他看我的眼神就好像  我是笑
And then they look at me like I'm a joke, right?
搞得我都岩勺约菏笑
Which makes me start to think that I am a joke,
然后我就_始失去方向
and then I start spinning.
我甚至再也搞不清@部蛟谥v什么
I don't even know what the play's about anymore.
P文  你最初x”rX得是v什么的
Kevin, what did you think it was about when you first read it?
@不重...  @不重要  @在...
You know, it doesn't ma-- it doesn't matter, it's...
你想f@太傻了
You're just gonna think it's stupid.
青蛙酒吧
愚蠢的拉布拉多f的
Said the dopey Labrador.
我倮了
We did it!
如果要在你和生孩子之g做x  我x你
If it's between you and having kids, you win.
每次如此
Every time.
毫o疑
No question.
我爸爸
My father,
他坶烨龠^一切
he loved football more than anything.
大多r候  他根本
Most of the time, he-he pretty much
就不怎么理我
didn't want anything to do with me.
可是...  如果他在看球
But... if he was watching football,
他我坐好
he let me sit
和他一起看球
and watch the game with him.
每我坐在地板上r
As long as I'd sit on the floor
我缀跻谎圆话l
and I didn't talk too much.
我是在想  以后我有了孩子
I always imagined that when I had kids
我也和他一起看球
that I'd watch the games with them, too.
但是我他f
Except I-I'd let them talk...
想f多大都行
as loud as they wanted.
我不知道自己是怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me.
你一c}也]有  小
God, there's nothing wrong with you, Bec.
和我同g的朋友都有孩子了
All of my friends my age have kids.
每一都有了
Every single one of them.
可是...
And...
也S是因槲疫在青蛙酒吧唱歌
maybe it's 'cause I'm still singing at Froggy's
而且我X得我不蚋褡龈改
and I'm not as far along as I thought I would be.
我不知道
I don't know.
事就是  每我]上眼
'Cause the truth is, when I close my eyes
想象我的未...
and I think about our future...
我看我在Ш⒆  杰克
I see us with kids, Jack.
是啊
Yeah.
我就是...
I just...
我喜g我的生活
I love our life.
就喜gF在的生活
I love it right now.
我很怕有改
And I'm so scared of changing it.
我不去改我的生活
I don't want to change it.
好  我o法容忍我之g有任何改
Okay? I'm not gonna stand for anything changing between us.
我之g的感情  就你和我
Okay? What we have together, you and me.
什么都不改
Nothing.
我很抱歉整天o你毫
Look, I'm sorry about pressuring you all day.
我只是...
I just...
我只想要你
I just want you.
人A了超杯
The Steelers won the Super Bowl.
Steelers won the Super Bowl.
布拉德肖A得了最佳球T
Bradshaw won MVP.
我的天[男人]My man.
是
Yes.
我是
I am.
你是
You are.
好
?Okay.
那么
So, uh...
你今天怎么回事
what was all that about today?
我f了  我想自己看比
I told you I wanted to watch the game by myself.
那你槭裁赐意^
Then why did you agree to come over?
不知道
I don't know.
因槲也幌
'Cause I didn't want to...
看起硐怪咖
seem like a weirdo.
好  我F在知道了
Okay. So, now I know.
不能在橄烨蛸季的周末s你
No hanging out on Sundays during football season.
-知道了  -但重c不只是橄烨
- I got it. ?- But it's not just about football.
好吧  那重c是什么
Okay. What's it about then?
男〉酱
Okay. So, growing up,
我和我爸一起看匹堡人的比
I used to watch the Steelers with my dad.
每周末
Right? Every single Sunday,
直到我L大了
until I grew up and...
搬磉@里  就]了@T
I moved out here and I just got out of the habit.
直到2006年  美橄烨蚵盟冠
It wasn't until the 2006 AFC Championship
他跟丹佛野R比  得
when they played the Broncos. Do you remember?
不得
No.
好吧  之
Okay. Anyway,
我想和我爸一起看比
I wanted to watch 'em with my dad.
我看了  他A了
And I did. And they won.
然后他A了超碗
And then they won the Super Bowl.
我就是...
And I just...
@就是我F在的T
It's just-just what I do now.
我看匹堡人的比...
I watch the Steelers, and...
我和我爸一起看
I watch 'em with my dad.
他起硎不e的人
He sounds like a cool guy.
有rg介B一下我JR吧
I'd like to meet him sometime.
好
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
好
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
Um... ?All right.
我知道@有c}人
And I know it's gonna be a little creepy.
@是你爸
This is your dad?
杰克
Jack.
我知道@起砗艹逗苓d
I know it sounds crazy and lame,
但我家很重橄烨  特e重
but football is a really big part of my family. Like, really big.
如果不是因殚烨  我都不出生
Like, I wouldn't even be here if it wasn't for football.
我是超碗比r  在l生g焉狭宋
I was conceived in a bathroom during the Super Bowl.
抱歉我之前B度不好
Sorry if I was a jerk before.
你真不打算原我
You're really not gonna forgive me?
好吧
Okay.
那如果我告V你
What if I told you a-a secret
一我]跟人f^的秘密呢
that I've never shared with anyone before?
ff看吧
We're listening.
好  行
Okay. All right.
但你得保C不告Ve人
But you got to promise not to tell anyone though, okay?
我要f的事很私密
This is a very private thing that I'm sharing with you.
是你和黛米・洛瓦托[歌手]交往的事
Is this about you dating Demi Lovato?
因榇蠹叶贾道@事
Because everyone knows.
不是  不是黛米・洛瓦托的事
No. You know what, it's not about Demi Lovato,
而且我跟她只是普通朋友  我...
and we were just friends. I just...
我有r候
Sometimes I... paint.
l都不知道@事  你P特姑姑也不知道
Now, no one knows this, not even your Aunt Kate,
我拿到”r
but... when I get a script,
第一件事就是把自己的感X出
the first thing I do is just sort of paint the way it makes me feel.
我第一次x了那”竞  就了@幅
I painted this after I read that play for the first time.
o
So...
我想我以前^你
I think I scared you before.
v什么鬼故事啊  死亡啊
Um, all that talk of ghosts and dying.
所有大人x^的故事
All that adult stuff we were reading about.
一些成人困惑的大人事情
That's some pretty confusing adult stuff.
所以
So, uh, you know,
我以槲疫^斫o你看我的
I thought I would come up here, show you my painting,
f一下我演那部虻闹黝}
tell you what I think my play is about.
因槲以谙
Because I was thinking, um,
@我都好受些
that it might make us all feel a little bit better.
但你不能笑我  好
But you got to promise not to make fun of me, okay?
那么
So, um...
我了@幅是因槲矣X得@部〉闹髦际巧活
Yeah, I painted this because I felt like the play was about life, you know?
生活充M了色彩
And life is full of color.
每人一路走
And we each get to come along
樯活砹俗约旱念色
and we add our own color to the painting.
M管@幅不是什么神作
You know? And even though it's not very big, the painting,
你得琢磨出l持m下午
you sort of have to figure that it goes on forever,
每方向都o限延伸下去
you know, in each direction. So, like, to infinity, you know?
因檫@就是生活  Π
'Cause that's kind of like life, right?
仔想想  其很不可思h
And it's really crazy, if you think about it, isn't it,
一百年前
that, a hundred years ago,
一我素未\面的人е行李箱淼竭@家
some guy that I never met came to this country with a suitcase.
他有一鹤
He has a son,
鹤佑钟鹤
who has a son,
鹤拥鹤佑钟鹤  就是我
who has me.
所以我一_始的r候
So, at first, when I was painting,
我r想  也W在@里
I was thinking, you know, maybe up here,
中@里是@人的起c
that was that guy's part of the painting and then, you know,
而我就在的@里
down here, that's my part of the painting.
然后我_始思考  如果...
And then I started to think, well, what if...
如果我都在布上呢
we're all in the painting, everywhere?
三小家伙
如果我出生前  命\就已被好了呢
And-and what if we're in the painting before we're born?
三小家伙
如果我死后才出F在上呢
What if we're in it after we die?
三小家伙
我添加的@些色
And these colors that we keep adding,
如果都只是相互g色的B加呢
what if they just keep getting added on top of one another,
直到最后我都成了同拥念色呢
until eventually we're not even different colors anymore?
我都只是一w的
We're just... one thing.
一幅
One painting.
-幸\帽  -幸\帽
- Lucky cap. - ?Lucky cap.
我爸不在我身了
I mean, my dad is not with us anymore.
他去世了  但他活在我心里
He's not alive, but he's with us.
未言
每天都活在我心里
He's with me every day.
一切都冥冥中自有安排
It all just sort of fits somehow.
即便你F在不知道何r何地
And even if you don't understand how yet,
我鄣娜私Kx世
people will die in our lives, people that we love.
也S在未
In the future.
也S在明天
Maybe tomorrow.
也S啄旰
Maybe years from now.
其挺美好的
I mean, it's kind of beautiful, right,
如果仔想想  就算一人死了
if you think about it, the fact that just because someone dies,
就算你不到@些人
just because you can't see them
不能再和他f
or talk to them anymore,
不代表中]有他的位置
it doesn't mean they're not still in the painting.
我想也S@就是全部的意x所在
I think maybe that's the point of the whole thing.
]有死亡
There's no dying.
]有为的你或我  或者他
There's no you or me or them.
我都是一w的
It's just us.
@幅...凌y的
And this... sloppy...
狂野的  色彩_的奇妙之
wild, colorful, magical thing
]有起c  也]有Kc
that has no beginning, it has no end...
@幅
this right here...
@就是我
I think it's us.
字幕M
ZiMuZu.tv
原翻g  pZ字幕
H供W 禁止用于任何商I盈利行
最新最快海外影字幕下d
登www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻g:  青椒  小泡椒  小尼克  小子
翻g:  桑葚  吸吸粒呀  劫Bobby
校:  劫Bobby  t
rgS:  格瑞特  ccisoda
后期:    精校&O:  tGabriel